protecting your family is your number
one priority ICICI Lombard presents the
perfect plan for you the family Shield
plan is comprehensive flexible unique it
covers more to protect more some of the
key features of this plan are infectious
disease benefit personal accident
benefit
flexibility family policy discount
tenure and renewal discount the
Infectious Disease benefit can be very
helpful as various illnesses have become
more common now it provides for coverage
against specific Vector bone diseases
rabes and tetus gastrointestinal
infections viral and nervous infections
personal accident benefit is a key
factor for protection it covers death
and disabilities adventure sports broken
bones and children's education grant
this plan offers you what you need you
can opt for any one of more base
benefits under one or more sections you
will be eligible for the base benefits
and or extensions if premium has been
paid once's more multiple add-on covers
to choose from are available too this
plan offers you a tenure and renewal
discount too you can get a policy term
of up to 3 years with long-term discount
you also get a 5% renewal discount the
renewal premium must be paid on or
before the policy expiry date or within
30 days that's not all you get a family
policy discount of up to 7.5% too give
your family the protection they deserve
and give yourself a hassle-free claim
experience too with icic Lombard's
family Shield plan you are our priority